http://www.gotyourback.com/privacy-policy.aspx

GotYourBack Privacy Policy
Your information is always safe with us. We will never rent, share or sell your information to any outside party.
Nothing is more important to GotYourBack than protecting the private information of visitors to our site. Below you'll find information about our commitment to ensuring the privacy of your personally identifiable information (such as your full name, address, e-mail address, telephone number and/or other identifying information) and preserving the integrity of the medium.
Please read on for more details about our privacy policy. If you have any questions or concerns, please send us an e-mail at info@gotyourback.com.
Online Information Collection
When you place an order, in order to process the request properly, we need to know your name, e-mail address, mailing address, credit card number, and its expiration date. This allows us to process and fulfill your order and to notify you of your order status.
We personalize your shopping experience by using your purchases to shape our recommendations about the merchandise that might be of interest to you. We also monitor customer traffic patterns and site usage to help us develop the design and layout of the store.
We may also use the information we collect to occasionally notify you about important functionality changes to the web site, new GotYourBack services, and special offers we think you'll find valuable. If you would rather not receive this information, visit your GotYourBack Subscriptions page to change your preferences. Make sure to change your preferences for each account or e-mail address you have left with us.
We Protect Your Information
When you place orders or access your account information, we offer the use of a secure server. The secure server software (SSL) encrypts all information you input before it is sent to us. Furthermore, all of the customer data we collect is protected against any kind of unauthorized access.
The Disclosure of Information
GotYourBack will never willfully disclose any personally identifiable information about our audience to any third party without first receiving the user's permission.
We Have Your Best Interests at Heart
We are committed to protecting your privacy to the utmost. We only use the information we collect on our own site to make shopping at GotYourBack as trouble free and convenient as possible, and to enhance your overall shopping experience. We will never sell, trade, or rent your personal information to others.
AGREEMENT
BY USING OUR WEB SITE, YOU FULLY CONSENT TO THE COLLECTION AND USE OF THIS INFORMATION BY GOTYOURBACK. IF WE DECIDE TO CHANGE OUR PRIVACY POLICY, WE WILL POST THOSE CHANGES ON THIS PAGE SO THAT YOU ARE ALWAYS AWARE OF WHAT INFORMATION WE COLLECT, HOW WE USE IT, AND UNDER WHAT CIRCUMSTANCES WE DISCLOSE IT.
GotYourBack welcomes your questions and comments about privacy issues, and how we can better serve you. Please send e-mail to info@gotyourback.com.
GotYourBack Security Policy
Nothing is more important to GotYourBack than protecting the private information of visitors to our site. Below you'll find information about our commitment to ensuring the privacy of your personally identifiable information (such as your full name, address, e-mail address, telephone number and/or other identifying information) and preserving the integrity of the medium.
Please read on for more details about our security policy. If you have any questions or concerns, please send us an e-mail at info@gotyourback.com.
Online Information Collection
When you place an order, in order to process the request properly, we need to know your name, e-mail address, mailing address, credit card number, and its expiration date. This allows us to process and fulfill your order and to notify you of your order status.
We personalize your shopping experience by using your purchases to shape our recommendations about the merchandise that might be of interest to you. We also monitor customer traffic patterns and site usage to help us develop the design and layout of the store.
We may also use the information we collect to occasionally notify you about important functionality changes to the web site, new GotYourBack services, and special offers we think you'll find valuable. If you would rather not receive this information, visit your GotYourBack Subscriptions page to change your preferences. Make sure to change your preferences for each account or e-mail address you have left with us.
We Protect Your Information
When you place orders or access your account information, we offer the use of a secure server. The secure server software (SSL) encrypts all information you input before it is sent to us. Furthermore, all of the customer data we collect is protected against any kind of unauthorized access.
The Disclosure of Information
GotYourBack will never willfully disclose any personally identifiable information about our audience to any third party without first receiving the user's permission.
We Have Your Best Interests at Heart
We are committed to protecting your privacy to the utmost. We only use the information we collect on our own site to make shopping at GotYourBack as trouble free and convenient as possible, and to enhance your overall shopping experience. We will never sell, trade, or rent your personal information to others.
Why GotYourBack is Safe
Our SSL secure server software is among the industry standard and some of the best software available for today's demanding e-commerce sites. By encrypting all of your personal and credit information, including your card number, name, and address, it cannot be read by anyone attempting to gain your information via computer. Also, when shoping at GotYourBack, you'll be one in a large number of customers who have already safely shopped with us without any instances of credit card fraud.
Guarantee Details:
Under the Fair Credit Billing Act, your bank cannot hold you liable for more than $50.00 of fraudulent charges. If your bank does hold you liable for any of this $50.00, GotYourBack will cover the entire liability for you, up to the full $50.00. GotYourBack will cover this liability only if the unauthorized use of your credit card resulted through no fault of your own from purchases made at GotYourBack while using the secure server. In the event of unauthorized use of your credit card, you must notify your credit card provider in accordance with its reporting rules and procedures.
AGREEMENT
BY USING OUR WEB SITE, YOU FULLY CONSENT TO THE COLLECTION AND USE OF THIS INFORMATION BY GOTYOURBACK. IF WE DECIDE TO CHANGE OUR SECURITY POLICY, WE WILL POST THOSE CHANGES ON THIS PAGE.
GotYourBack welcomes your questions and comments about security issues, and how we can better serve you. Please send e-mail to info@gotyourback.com.
Join our mailing list to receive the latest offers, updates & promotions!
Email Address:
Showroom Hours:
© 2014 GotYourBack.com. All Rights Reserved. eCommerce Store Design by Solid Cactus
